{"data":[{"question":"He suggested that the newcomer ___ his medical report soon.","a":"submit","b":"submitted","c":"has submitted","d":"would submit","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The Subjunctive is used after the following verbs:to advise (that); to ask (that); to command (that); to demand (that); to desire (that); to insist (that); to propose (that), to recommend (that); to request (that); to suggest (that); to urge (that) \n- Structure: advise, ask, suggest (that) somebody do something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"What did the girl look like ? \" She wore a wedding dress ___ she were a bride.\"","a":"like","b":"so","c":"so that","d":"as if","answer":"4","explain":"\n- As if: in a way that makes it seem that something is true or that something is happening","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"As a matter of fact, I don't like the lady. \" If the lady ___ actually a bother, I'll take her home\"","a":"are","b":"was","c":"is","d":"were","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The lady - is","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I didn't catch the train. \" You _________ the train if you had hurried.\"","a":"would catch","b":"had caught","c":"could have caught","d":"could catch","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Could have PP: used to say that something was a possibility in the past, but did not actually happen","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The teacher demands that everyone ___ in his seat at nine o'clock.","a":"will be","b":"be","c":"were","d":"shall be","answer":"2","explain":"\n- The Subjunctive is used after the following verbs:to advise (that); to ask (that); to command (that); to demand (that); to desire (that); to insist (that); to propose (that), to recommend (that); to request (that); to suggest (that); to urge (that) \n- Structure: advise, ask, suggest (that)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"If the car ___ no good, I would have to buy another one.","a":"were","b":"is","c":"was","d":"are","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 3: It is impossible that the condition will be fulfilled because it refers to the past. \n- Form: if + Past Perfect, Conditional II (= would + have + Past Participle)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Did you work yesterday? \" I wish yesterday ___ a holiday.\"","a":"is","b":"was","c":"were","d":"had been","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Wish + had + pp: It is impossible that the condition will be fulfilled because it refers to the past.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"You didn't go to the party, did you? \" I do wish I ___ there \"","a":"was","b":"were","c":"had been","d":"went","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Wish + had + pp: It is impossible that the condition will be fulfilled because it refers to the past.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I would have gone swimming, if I ___ a swimming suit-","a":"had had","b":"have had","c":"had","d":"have","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 3: It is impossible that the condition will be fulfilled because it refers to the past. \n- Form: if + Past Perfect, Conditional II (= would + have + Past Participle) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"What would you have done if you ___ to work yesterday?","a":"didn't have","b":"hadn't had","c":"didn't","d":"didn't have had","answer":"2","explain":"- Conditional Sentence Type 3: It is impossible that the condition will be fulfilled because it refers to the past.\n\n-Form: if + Past Perfect, Conditional II (= would + have + Past Participle)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}